[('From', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump:', 'O'), ('Wishing', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('wonderful', 'O'), ('holiday', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('happy,', 'O'), ('healthy,', 'O'), ('prosperous', 'O'), ('New', 'O'), ('Year.', 'O'), ('Let’s', 'O'), ('think', 'O'), ('like', 'O'), ('champions', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('2010!', 'O')]
[('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('International', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Tower', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('ranked', 'O'), ('6th', 'O'), ('tallest', 'O'), ('building', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('world', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Council', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('on', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Tall', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Buildings', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Urban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Habitat', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('http:bit.lysqvQq', 'O')]
[('Wishing', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('yours', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('Happy', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Bountiful', 'O'), ('Thanksgiving!', 'O')]
[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Partners', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('TV1', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('New', 'O'), ('Reality', 'O'), ('Series', 'O'), ('Entitled,', 'O'), ("Omarosa's", 'O'), ('Ultimate', 'O'), ('Merger:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comyk5m3lc', 'O')]
[('--Work', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('begun,', 'O'), ('ahead', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('schedule,', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('build', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('greatest', 'O'), ('golf', 'O'), ('course', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('history:', 'O'), ('Trump', 'O'), ('International', 'O'), ('–', 'O'), ('Scotland.', 'O')]
[('--From', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump:', 'O'), ('"Ivanka', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Jared’s', 'O'), ('wedding', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('spectacular,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('couple.', 'O'), ('I’m', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('proud', 'O'), ('father."', 'O')]
[('Hear', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('discuss', 'O'), ('big', 'O'), ('gov', 'O'), ('spending,', 'O'), ('banks,', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('taxes', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Your', 'O'), ('World', 'O'), ('wNeil', 'O'), ('Cavuto:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comyhnzd7p', 'O')]
[('Watch', 'O'), ('video', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Ivanka', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('sharing', 'O'), ('business', 'O'), ('advice', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('4', 'O'), ('entrepreneurial', 'O'), ('women', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('GMA:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comyk6hlfo', 'O')]
[('-', 'O'), ('Read', 'O'), ('what', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('has', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('say', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('daughter', 'O'), ("Ivanka's", 'O'), ('upcoming', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book,', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Trump', 'O'), ('Card:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comycsqmda', 'O')]
[('"A', 'O'), ('lot', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('imagination,', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ("can't", 'O'), ('execute--you', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('execute', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('imagination."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Read', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ("Trump's", 'O'), ('Top', 'O'), ('Ten', 'O'), ('Tips', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Success:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.commcn8yl', 'O')]
[('-', 'O'), ('More', 'O'), ('hysterical', 'O'), ('DSRL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('videos', 'O'), ('featuring', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('"Double', 'O'), ('Trump"', 'O'), ('plus', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('Golden', 'O'), ('Lick', 'O'), ('Race', 'O'), ('Sweepstakes:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.com6asujj', 'O')]
[('-', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('bids', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('buy', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Oreo', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Double', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Stuf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Racing', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('League.', 'O'), ('Check', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('out:', 'O'), ('http:www.nabiscoworld.comoreodsrlhome.aspx', 'O')]
[('Reminder:', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('competition', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('LIVE', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Bahamas', 'LOCATION'), ('-', 'O'), ('Tonight', 'O'), ('@', 'O'), ('9pm', 'O'), ('(EST)', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.commrzad9', 'O')]
[('Watch', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('competition', 'O'), ('LIVE', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Bahamas', 'LOCATION'), ('-', 'O'), ('Sunday,', 'O'), ('823', 'O'), ('@', 'O'), ('9pm', 'O'), ('(ET)', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.commrzad9', 'O')]
[('--', 'O'), ('Watch', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ("Trump's", 'PERSON'), ('recent', 'O'), ('appearance', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Late', 'O'), ('Show', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('David', 'PERSON'), ('Letterman:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comklts6b', 'O')]
[('Ivanka', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Twitter', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('You', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('follow', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('@IvankaTrump', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('Have', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('terrific', 'O'), ('weekend!', 'O')]
[('"Think.', 'O'), ('That’s', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('step.', 'O'), ('Use', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('power', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('utilize', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('develop', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('capability"', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Browse', 'PERSON'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ("Trump's", 'O'), ('Summer', 'O'), ('Reading', 'O'), ('List', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Business', 'O'), ('Success', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('University', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Blog:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comn5468r', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('list', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ("Trump's", 'O'), ('books', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('summer', 'O'), ('reading', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('University', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Blog:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comknyswt', 'O')]
[('Congrats', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('winners', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('around', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('world', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('entered', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('"Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('Champion"', 'O'), ('signed', 'O'), ('bookkeychain', 'O'), ('contest!', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('backs', 'O'), ("'Apprentice'", 'O'), ('Randal', 'PERSON'), ('Pinkett', 'PERSON'), ('for', 'O'), ('N.J.', 'LOCATION'), ('Lieutenant', 'O'), ('Governor:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.commvovzb', 'O')]
[('"Be', 'O'), ('aware', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('things', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('seem', 'O'), ('inexplicable', 'O'), ('because', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('big', 'O'), ('step', 'O'), ('towards', 'O'), ('innovation."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[("Here's", 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('safe', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('happy', 'O'), ('Independence', 'O'), ('Day', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('Enjoy', 'O'), ('it!', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
[('Watch', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('powerful', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('frank', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('about', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('economy', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Greta', 'PERSON'), ('Van', 'PERSON'), ("Susteren's", 'O'), ('On', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Record:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.commmjked', 'O')]
[('RE:', 'O'), ('Michael', 'O'), ('Jackson:', 'O'), ('"He', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('friend', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('spectacular', 'O'), ('entertainer.', 'O'), ('It’s', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('devastating', 'O'), ('loss!"', 'O'), ('-Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump’s', 'O'), ('commercial-free', 'O'), ('WWE', 'O'), ('Raw', 'O'), ('does', 'O'), ('big', 'O'), ('rating:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comnxvquo', 'O')]
[('“Expand', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('life', 'O'), ('every', 'O'), ('day.”', 'O'), ('–Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('-', 'O'), ('Wishing', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Happy', 'O'), ("Father's", 'O'), ('Day', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ("Dad's", 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('there', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('YOU', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('champion', 'O'), ('today', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('everyday!', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comkn95ju', 'O')]
[('RE:', 'O'), ('FB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Vanity', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('URLs:', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SF', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chronicle', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('-', 'O'), ('"David', 'O'), ('Beckham', 'PERSON'), ('was', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('first,', 'O'), ('along', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Britney', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Spears', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Donald', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump."', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comln4lol', 'O')]
[('Thanks', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('thoughtful', 'O'), ('birthday', 'O'), ('wishes', 'O'), ('–', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
[('Today', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ("Trump's", 'O'), ('Birthday!', 'O'), ('Send', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ("B'day", 'O'), ('wishes', 'O'), ('here:', 'O'), ('http:www.facebook.comDonaldTrump', 'O')]
[('Last', 'O'), ('week', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('"Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('Champion"', 'O'), ('signed', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('keychain', 'O'), ('contest:', 'O'), ('http:www.trumpthinklikeachampion.comcontest', 'O')]
[('“If', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ("don't", 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('problems,', 'O'), ("you're", 'O'), ('pretending', 'O'), ('or', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ("don't", 'O'), ('run', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('own', 'O'), ('business.”', 'O'), ('–Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ("Trump's", 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('iGoogle', 'O'), ('Showcase', 'O'), ('page:', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyDdD2A', 'O')]
[('"You', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('know', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('call', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('quits', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('keep', 'O'), ('moving', 'O'), ('forward."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:www.trumpthinklikeachampion.com', 'O')]
[('Read', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('excerpt', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('Champion', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump:', 'PERSON'), ('http:bit.ly11FHpR', 'PERSON')]
[('"Your', 'O'), ('higher', 'O'), ('self', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('direct', 'O'), ('opposition', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('comfort', 'O'), ('zone."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Did', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('know', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Facebook?', 'O'), ('http:www.facebook.comDonaldTrump', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('Become', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fan', 'O'), ('today!', 'O')]
[("Don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('"Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('Champion"', 'O'), ('signed', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('keychain', 'O'), ('contest:', 'O'), ('http:www.trumpthinklikeachampion.comcontest', 'O')]
[('"Keep', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('fast,', 'O'), ('short', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('direct', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('whatever', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Read', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('that', 'O'), ('appeared', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('New', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('York', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Times', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Magazine:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comqsx4o6', 'O')]
[('"Always', 'O'), ('know', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('could', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('precipice', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('something', 'O'), ('great."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('"...these', 'O'), ('days...we', 'O'), ('could', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('use', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('little', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('power', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Trumpative', 'O'), ('thinking."', 'O'), ('–BarnesandNoble.com', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('"We', 'O'), ('win', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('lives', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('having', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ("champion's", 'O'), ('view', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('each', 'O'), ('moment."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('"Don’t', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('afraid', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('unique', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ("it's", 'O'), ('like', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('afraid', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('self."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('"When', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('achiever', 'O'), ('achieves,', 'O'), ("it's", 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('plateau,', 'O'), ('it’s', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('beginning."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('"Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('Champion"', 'O'), ('signed', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('keychain', 'O'), ('contest:', 'O'), ('http:www.trumpthinklikeachampion.comcontest', 'O')]
[('"Strive', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('wholeness', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('keep', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('sense', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('wonder', 'O'), ('intact."', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('http:tinyurl.compqpfvm', 'O')]
[('Listen', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book,', 'O'), ('Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('Champion:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comqs24vl', 'O')]
[('Miss', 'O'), ('USA', 'O'), ('Tara', 'PERSON'), ('Conner', 'PERSON'), ('will', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('fired', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('"I\'ve', 'O'), ('always', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('believer', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('second', 'O'), ('chances."', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
[('"My', 'O'), ('persona', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('never', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('wallflower', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('I’d', 'O'), ('rather', 'O'), ('build', 'O'), ('walls', 'O'), ('than', 'O'), ('cling', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('them"', 'O'), ('--Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]
[('New', 'O'), ('Blog', 'O'), ('Post:', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('Finale', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Lessons', 'O'), ('Learned', 'O'), ('Along', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Way:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comqlux5e', 'O')]
[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('reads', 'O'), ('Top', 'O'), ('Ten', 'O'), ('Financial', 'O'), ('Tips', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Late', 'O'), ('Show', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('David', 'PERSON'), ('Letterman:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comooafwn', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('Very', 'O'), ('funny!', 'O')]
[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('appearing', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('View', 'O'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('morning', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('discuss', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('Champion!', 'O')]
[('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('watch', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('on', 'O'), ('Late', 'O'), ('Night', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('David', 'PERSON'), ('Letterman', 'PERSON'), ('as', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('presents', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Top', 'O'), ('Ten', 'O'), ('List', 'O'), ('tonight!', 'O')]
[('WIshing', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('happy,', 'O'), ('healthy', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('prosperous', 'O'), ('New', 'O'), ('Year!', 'O')]
[('Wishing', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('Happy', 'O'), ('Holiday', 'O'), ('season!', 'O')]
[("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('appearing', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Larry', 'O'), ('King', 'O'), ('Live', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('final', 'O'), ('show,', 'O'), ('Thursday', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.,', 'O'), ('CNN.', 'O'), ("Larry's", 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('TV', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('25', 'O'), ('years...', 'O')]
[('...Trump', 'O'), ('International', 'O'), ('Hotel', 'O'), ('Las', 'O'), ('Vegas,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('International', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel', 'LOCATION'), ('&', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION'), ('Waikiki', 'LOCATION'), ('Beach', 'LOCATION'), ('Walk.', 'O'), ('http:tlworldsbest.roiresearch.com.', 'O')]
[('Those', 'O'), ('five', 'O'), ('hotels', 'O'), ('includeTrump', 'O'), ('International', 'O'), ('Hotel', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('Tower', 'O'), ('New', 'O'), ('York,', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Soho', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('York,', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('International', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Tower', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chicago...', 'O')]
[('All', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hotels', 'O'), ('currently', 'O'), ('open', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Collection', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('have', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('nominated', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Travel', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ("Leisure's", 'O'), ('"World\'s', 'O'), ('Best', 'O'), ('Awards', 'O'), ('2011"', 'O'), ('.....', 'O')]
[('Congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Brandy', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Clint', 'PERSON'), ('for', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('player.', 'O'), ("It's", 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('terrific', 'O'), ('season!', 'O')]
[('Tonight', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('finale---and', 'O'), ("it's", 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('every', 'O'), ('way,', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('Liza', 'PERSON'), ('Minnelli', 'PERSON'), ('performing', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('Apprentice!', 'O')]
[("Tonight's", 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ("ever--we're", 'O'), ('down', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('final', 'O'), ('3,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ("it's", 'O'), ('high', 'O'), ('excitement', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('way.', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O')]
[('Congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Evan', 'PERSON'), ('Lysacek', 'PERSON'), ('for', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('nominated', 'O'), ('SI', 'O'), ('sportsman', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('year.', 'O'), ("He's", 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('guy,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('vote!', 'O'), ('#EvanForSI', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('wishes', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Happy', 'O'), ('Thanksgiving!', 'O')]
[('Tomorrow', 'O'), ("night's", 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('delivers', 'O'), ('excitement', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('QVC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('along', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('appearances', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Isaac', 'PERSON'), ('Mizrahi', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Cathie', 'PERSON'), ('Black.', 'PERSON'), ('10', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
[('Watch', 'O'), ('CNN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('2', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('5', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Friday', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('7', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('11', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Thanksgiving', 'O'), ('Special', 'O'), ('hosted', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('John', 'PERSON'), ('King.', 'O'), ("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('featured', 'O'), ('guest.', 'O')]
[('Staff', 'O'), ('Sgt.', 'O'), ('Salvatore', 'PERSON'), ('A.', 'PERSON'), ('Giunta', 'PERSON'), ('received', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Medal', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Honor', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Pres.', 'O'), ('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('this', 'O'), ('month.', 'O'), ('It', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('honor', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('visit', 'O'), ('me', 'O'), ('today.', 'O')]
[('"CNBC', 'O'), ('Titans:', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('"', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('shown', 'O'), ('Friday', 'O'), ('Nov', 'O'), ('19th', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('1', 'O'), ('am,', 'O'), ('Sunday', 'O'), ('1121', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('1124', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('7', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyckojPN', 'O')]
[("We're", 'O'), ('getting', 'O'), ('down', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('wire', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice--tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('action!', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('week', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Greta', 'PERSON'), ('van', 'PERSON'), ('Susteren', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('available', 'O'), ('here', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('slightly', 'O'), ('abridged', 'O'), ('form.', 'O'), ('http:bit.ly96ztOA', 'O'), ('Good', 'O'), ('info', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('know', 'O'), ('about.', 'O')]
[("Tonight's", 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('big', 'O'), ('surprise', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('top', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('show', 'O'), ('--', 'O'), ("don't", 'O'), ('miss', 'O'), ('it!', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O')]
[("Tonight's", 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ("won't", 'O'), ('want', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('miss!', 'O'), ('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in--10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O')]
[("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('variety', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('topics', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Greta', 'PERSON'), ('Van', 'PERSON'), ('Susteren,', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Fox', 'O'), ('News.', 'O'), ('It', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('part', 'O'), ('series.', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('View', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('morning.', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('talked', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice.', 'O'), ("Tonight's", 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('one--tough,', 'O'), ('exciting', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('surprising.', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('pmNBC', 'O')]
[('Be', 'O'), ('prepared', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('sensational', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('night,', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O')]
[("Don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('unpredictable', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('exciting', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice--', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC', 'ORGANIZATION')]
[('An', 'O'), ('HR', 'O'), ('solutions', 'O'), ('company', 'O'), ('polled', 'O'), ('1,000', 'O'), ('employed', 'O'), ('adults', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('find', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('would', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('ideal', 'O'), ('bosses...', 'O'), ('http:bit.ly9uP9vj', 'O')]
[('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('watch', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('tonight,', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ("NBC--it's", 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ("won't", 'O'), ('forget!', 'O')]
[('Scotland', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Internatonal', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Golf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Links-Scotland', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('progressing', 'O'), ('beautifully', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('well.', 'O'), ('http:bit.lybUWWNb', 'O')]
[("Don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('exciting', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice--10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O')]
[("I'm", 'O'), ('honored', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('presented', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('award', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Doctor', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Business', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Administration', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Honoris', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Causa', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('from', 'O'), ('Robert', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Gordon', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('University', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('Aberdeen,', 'LOCATION'), ('Scotland', 'LOCATION')]
[('Read', 'O'), ("Ivanka's", 'O'), ('blog', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ("night's", 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Entertainment', 'O'), ('Weekly', 'O'), ('...http:bit.lybMNF72', 'O')]
[('Tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('for', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('exciting', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('--', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Dog', 'O'), ('Whisperer', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('appearance.', 'O')]
[('See', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('sizzle', 'O'), ('reel', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyax8nah', 'O')]
[("Don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('for', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('action', 'O'), ('packed', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice.', 'O'), ('http:bit.lybnAuAv', 'O')]
[('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ("Melania's", 'O'), ('second', 'O'), ('QVC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('show', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('"Melania', 'O'), ('Timepieces', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('Jewelry"', 'O'), ('tonight,', 'O'), ('live', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('9-10', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('QVC', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyaDdvKj', 'O')]
[("Don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('hour', 'O'), ('premiere', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice.', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('EST', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O'), ("We're", 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('season!', 'O')]
[('Eric', 'PERSON'), ('did', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('job', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('Eric', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Foundation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('annual', 'O'), ('charity', 'O'), ('outing.', 'O'), ("I'm", 'O'), ('proud', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('him.', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyc1y3c3', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('am', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('happy', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('civilian', 'O'), ('version', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('"The', 'O'), ('Apprentice"', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('air', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('fall.', 'O'), ('There', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('excitement', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('well', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('opportunity.', 'O')]
[('Coming', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('soon:', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('hour', 'O'), ('premiere', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice.', 'O'), ('Next', 'O'), ('Thursday,', 'O'), ('September', 'O'), ('16th,', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O'), ('http:bit.lybMB4CH', 'O')]
[("There's", 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('lot', 'O'), ('going', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Eric', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Foundation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('...', 'O'), ('http:bit.ly9rJ0sn', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('invited', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Caroline', 'PERSON'), ('Wozniacki', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('sit', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('family', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('special', 'O'), ('box', 'O'), ('during', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('match', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('U.S.', 'O'), ('Open', 'O'), ('yesterday.', 'O'), ("She's", 'O'), ('fantastic!', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('International', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel', 'LOCATION'), ('&', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('--spectacular!', 'O'), ('http:www.trump.comHotel_CollectionTrump_New_yorkTrump_New_York.asp', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ("Serta's", 'O'), ('Counting', 'O'), ('Sheep', 'O'), ('(and', 'O'), ('me)', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('International', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel', 'LOCATION'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('http:bit.lySertaRm9', 'O')]
[("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Late', 'O'), ('Show', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('David', 'PERSON'), ('Letterman', 'PERSON'), ('tonight--be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('show.', 'O'), ('11:30', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('CBS.', 'O')]
[('Went', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Yankees', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('game', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Bill', 'PERSON'), ("O'Reilly--we", 'PERSON'), ('had', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('watching', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Yankees', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('win!', 'O')]
[('Spent', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('weekend', 'O'), ('golfing', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('National', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Golf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Westchester', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('National', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Golf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bedminster.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('Pageant', 'O'), ('raked', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('ratings!', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('job', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('everyone.', 'O')]
[('Congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Mexico,', 'O'), ('Jimena', 'PERSON'), ('Navarrete,', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('2010,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('show.', 'O')]
[("It's", 'O'), ('going', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('hotter', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas', 'LOCATION'), ('tonight!', 'O'), ('Watch', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('Pageant', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ("I'm", 'O'), ('looking', 'O'), ('forward', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('there!', 'O')]
[('Four', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('days', 'O'), ('until', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('Pageant.', 'O'), ('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Monday', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC--it', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('amazing', 'O'), ('show.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('original', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('returns', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('hour', 'O'), ('premiere', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Thursday', 'O'), ('September', 'O'), ('16th.', 'O'), ('Looking', 'O'), ('forward', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('season!', 'O')]
[('So', 'O'), ("don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Serta', 'O'), ('Counting', 'O'), ('Sheep', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Hire', 'O'), ('contest!', 'O'), ('www.youtube.comusermattressserta', 'O')]
[('That', 'O'), ('trip', 'O'), ('would', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('International', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel', 'LOCATION'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas...http:www.trump.comHotel_CollectionTrump_Las_VegasTrump_Las_Vegas.asp', 'LOCATION')]
[('Friday', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Counting', 'O'), ('Sheep', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Hire', 'O'), ('contest.', 'O'), ('Click', 'O'), ('here', 'O'), ('www.youtube.comusermattressserta', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('could', 'O'), ('win', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('trip', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('webisode', 'O'), ('www.youtube.comusermattressserta', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('3', 'O'), ('part', 'O'), ('series', 'O'), ('featuring', 'O'), ('me', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Serta.', 'O'), ('Which', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('favorite?', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('webisode', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('3', 'O'), ('part', 'O'), ('series', 'O'), ('featuring', 'O'), ('me', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Serta.', 'O'), ('Which', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('favorite?', 'O'), ('www.youtube.comusermattressserta', 'O')]
[("Eric's", 'O'), ('Sept.', 'O'), ('14th', 'O'), ('event', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('held', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('National', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Golf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Westchester.', 'O'), ('http:www.trump.comGolf_ClubsWestchesterWestchester.asp', 'O')]
[('Mark', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('calenders', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('August', 'O'), ('23rd:', 'O'), ('http:www.missuniverse.com', 'O')]
[('Performing', 'O'), ('live', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('Pageant', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Mandalay', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bay', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Resort', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Casino', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('Telemundo,', 'O'), ('Orianthi,', 'O'), ('John', 'O'), ('Legend', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Roots.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('Pageant', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('August', 'O'), ('23', 'O'), ('(9-11', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC,', 'O'), ('ET)', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Bret', 'PERSON'), ('Michaels', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Natalie', 'PERSON'), ('Morales', 'PERSON'), ('to', 'O'), ('co-host,', 'O'), ('live', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas', 'LOCATION')]
[('Enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('contest....http:www.facebook.comsertamattress...and', 'O'), ('stay', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('International', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel', 'LOCATION'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas', 'LOCATION')]
[('and', 'O'), ('stay', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('International', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel', 'LOCATION'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas', 'LOCATION'), ('...http:www.trump.comHotel_CollectionTrump_Las_VegasTrump_Las_Vegas.asp', 'O')]
[("I'm", 'O'), ('helping', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Serta', 'O'), ('Counting', 'O'), ('Sheep', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('work.', 'O'), ('Enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('contest', 'O'), ('http:www.facebook.comsertamattress', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('win', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('trip', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas..', 'LOCATION')]
[('Could', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('newest', 'O'), ('apprentice?', 'O'), ('http:www.youtube.comuserMattressSerta', 'O'), ('...Enter', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('contest', 'O'), ('..', 'O'), ('.http:www.facebook.comsertamattress', 'O')]
[("I'm", 'O'), ('proud', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('accept', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('2010', 'O'), ('HollyRod', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Foundation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Humanitarian', 'O'), ('Award', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Holly', 'PERSON'), ('Robinson', 'PERSON'), ('Peete,', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('raised', 'O'), ('$700,000', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O')]
[('and', 'O'), ('yet', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('...all', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('spectacular.', 'O'), ('http:www.trump.comGolf_ClubsWestchesterWestchester.asp', 'O')]
[('and', 'O'), ("here's", 'O'), ('another....http:www.trump.comGolf_ClubsColts_NeckColts_Neck.asp', 'O')]
[('Visited', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('golf', 'O'), ('courses', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('weekend...this', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('one...http:www.trump.comGolf_ClubsHudson_ValleyHudson_Valley.asp', 'O')]
[('George', 'PERSON'), ('Steinbrenner', 'PERSON'), ('was', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('friend', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('true', 'O'), ('legend.', 'O'), ('There', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('never', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('anyone', 'O'), ('like', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York.', 'LOCATION'), ("We've", 'O'), ('lost', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('truly', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('man.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('edition', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Thursdays', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('fall', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ("ET---I'm", 'O'), ('putting', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('work!', 'O')]
[('Due', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('popular', 'O'), ('demand,', 'O'), ('CNN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('will', 'O'), ('re-broadcast', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Larry', 'O'), ('King', 'O'), ('Live', 'O'), ('show', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('hosted', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('June,', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('Larry.', 'O'), ('Monday', 'O'), ('July', 'O'), ('5,', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('CNN', 'ORGANIZATION')]
[('Wishing', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('wonderful', 'O'), ('Independence', 'O'), ('Day', 'O'), ('weekend.', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('lot', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('thankful', 'O'), ('for.', 'O')]
[('Work', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('expected', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('begin', 'O'), ('today', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('golf', 'O'), ('course', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Scotland.', 'O'), ('It', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('spectacular!', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyblp1Tq', 'O')]
[('"Trading', 'O'), ('Shots', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump"--a', 'PERSON'), ('great', 'O'), ('article', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Wall', 'O'), ('Street', 'O'), ('Journal', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyc9eZbq', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Eric', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Foundation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('has', 'O'), ('raised', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('$1,000,000', 'O'), ('towards', 'O'), ('St.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Jude', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("Children's", 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Research', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hospital.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('http:twitter.comEricTrumpFdn', 'O')]
[('Great', 'O'), ('job', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Larry', 'O'), ('King', 'O'), ('Live', 'O'), ('Gulf', 'O'), ('Telethon', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('night--$1.3', 'O'), ('million', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('raised', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('2', 'O'), ('hours.', 'O')]
[('For', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('information', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ("tonight's", 'O'), ('two', 'O'), ('hour', 'O'), ('telethon,', 'O'), ('8', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.:', 'O'), ('http:twitter.comkingsthings', 'O')]
[('Tonight', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('watch', 'O'), ('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Ivanka', 'PERSON'), ('on', 'O'), ('Larry', 'O'), ('King', 'O'), ('Live', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Relief', 'O'), ('Telethon', 'O'), ('http:larrykinglive.blogs.cnn.com', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Ultimate', 'O'), ('Merger:', 'O'), ('http:www.nydailynews.comentertainmenttv201006172010-06-17_omarosa_is_back_and_this_time_its_personal.html', 'O')]
[('Tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('TV', 'O'), ('One', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('"The', 'O'), ('Ultimate', 'O'), ('Merger"', 'O'), ('starring', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('only', 'O'), ('Omarosa', 'LOCATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('twelve', 'O'), ('brave', 'O'), ('bachelors', 'O'), ('...', 'O')]
[('And', 'O'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('SoHo', 'O'), ('New', 'LOCATION'), ('York', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hottest', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('hotels', 'O'), ('anywhere....', 'O'), ('http:www.trump.comHotel_CollectionTrump_SoHoTrump_SoHo.asp', 'O')]
[('Had', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('dinner', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Quattro,', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('SoHo', 'LOCATION'), ('Hotel.', 'O'), ("It's", 'O'), ('already', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('hottest', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('restaurants', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('city.', 'O')]
[('WSJ', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('covers', 'O'), ('Ride', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Fame', 'O'), ('http:online.wsj.comarticleSB10001424052748704575304575297082506166258.html?mod=WSJ_NY_RealEstate_MIDDLE_LSMini', 'O')]
[('Rima', 'PERSON'), ('Fakih,', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('USA,', 'O'), ('rode', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('me', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Gray', 'O'), ('Line', 'O'), ('Ride', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Fame', 'O'), ('yesterday...', 'O'), ('http:www.missuniverse.commissusa', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('Gray', 'O'), ("Line's", 'O'), ('site', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Ride', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Fame...', 'O'), ('http:www.newyorksightseeing.com', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('am', 'O'), ('honored', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('chosen', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Gray', 'O'), ('Line', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('NY', 'O'), ('Ride', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Fame', 'O'), ('Campaign.', 'O'), ('Today', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ribbon', 'O'), ('cutting', 'O'), ('ceremony', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('front', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower.', 'LOCATION')]
[('Tonight', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('trade', 'O'), ('places', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Larry', 'PERSON'), ('King', 'PERSON'), ('@kingsthings', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('25th', 'O'), ('anniversary', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('show.', 'O'), ('9PM', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('CNN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('featuring', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('clips.', 'O')]
[('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('watch', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Larry', 'O'), ('King', 'O'), ('Show', 'O'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('CNN,', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('host,', 'O'), ('Larry', 'PERSON'), ('the', 'O'), ('guest.', 'O'), ('http:larrykinglive.blogs.cnn.com', 'O')]
[('Checking', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('course', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('TNGC', 'LOCATION'), ('Westchester', 'LOCATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('fantastic.', 'O'), ('Should', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('season.', 'O'), ('http:www.trumpnationalwestchester.com', 'O')]
[("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('turning', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('table', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Larry', 'PERSON'), ('King', 'PERSON'), ('this', 'O'), ('Saturday', 'O'), ('night.', 'O'), ("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('interviewing', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('honor', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('25th', 'O'), ('Anniversary', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('show.', 'O')]
[('Wishing', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Happy', 'O'), ('Memorial', 'O'), ('Day', 'O'), ('Weekend,', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('special', 'O'), ('thought', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('veterans', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('done', 'O'), ('so', 'O'), ('much', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('freedom.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Dunes', 'O'), ('here', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('amazing,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ("they're", 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('learned', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('geomorphology,', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('study', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('movement', 'O'), ('landforms.', 'O'), ("We've", 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('trip', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('North', 'O'), ('Coast', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Scotland', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('spectacular--the', 'O'), ('sea,', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('sand', 'O'), ('dunes,', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('rolling', 'O'), ('bluffs--we', 'O'), ('walked', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('course', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('fantastic.', 'O')]
[('Scotland', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('beautiful.', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('spent', 'O'), ('several', 'O'), ('years', 'O'), ('looking', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('right', 'O'), ('place,', 'O'), ('visiting', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('200', 'O'), ('sites,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('absolutely', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('right', 'O'), ('place!', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('ratings', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('were', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('had', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('time.', 'O'), ('It', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('terrific', 'O'), ('season', 'O'), ('--', 'O'), ('congrats', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('everyone!', 'O')]
[('Ivanka', 'PERSON'), ('caught', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Bret', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Holly', 'PERSON'), ('backstage.', 'O'), ('Both', 'O'), ('Bret', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Holly', 'PERSON'), ('were', 'O'), ('champions', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('way.', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyckmKKU', 'O')]
[('Congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Bret', 'PERSON'), ('Michaels,', 'PERSON'), ('the', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice.', 'O'), ("Bret's", 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('true', 'O'), ('champion,', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('us', 'O'), ('were', 'O'), ('happy', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('win!', 'O')]
[("Who's", 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('pick--@bretmichaels', 'O'), ('or', 'O'), ('@hollyrpeete', 'O'), ('?', 'O'), ('Vote', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ("Ivanka's", 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('Facebook', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('page!', 'O'), ('http:ow.ly1NfMt', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('latest', 'O'), ('update', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Bret', 'PERSON'), ('Michaels', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ("he's", 'O'), ('making', 'O'), ('every', 'O'), ('effort', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('attend', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('live', 'O'), ('finale', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Sunday--so', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in!', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ("Ivanka's", 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('FaceBook', 'O'), ('page', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('keep', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ("what's", 'O'), ('happening--from', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice,', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('jewlery', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('free', 'O'), ('tickets', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('more..', 'O')]
[('Put', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('calendar:', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('live', 'O'), ('finale', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('Sunday', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O'), ('Who', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('next', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice?', 'O')]
[('Congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('USA,', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('Rima', 'PERSON'), ('Fakih.', 'PERSON'), ('Rima', 'PERSON'), ('will', 'O'), ('represent', 'O'), ('us', 'O'), ('well', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('Universe', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('wonderful', 'O'), ('Miss', 'LOCATION'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('.', 'O')]
[('Looking', 'O'), ('forward', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('2010', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('Pageant,', 'O'), ('Sunday', 'O'), ('May', 'O'), ('16', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC,', 'O'), ('7', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('ET,', 'O'), ('hosted', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Curtis', 'PERSON'), ('Stone', 'PERSON'), ('&', 'O'), ('Natalie', 'PERSON'), ('Morales', 'PERSON'), ('live', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas.', 'LOCATION')]
[("We're", 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('happy', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('hear', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Bret', 'O'), ("Michael's", 'O'), ('progress', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('send', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('wishes', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('full', 'O'), ('recovery.', 'O')]
[('Providing', 'O'), ('backstage', 'O'), ('commentary', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Miss', 'LOCATION'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('Pageant', 'LOCATION'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('comedic', 'O'), ('mother-daughter', 'O'), ('duo', 'O'), ('Joan', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('Rivers.', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('lineup!', 'O')]
[('Also', 'O'), ('appearing', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Miss', 'LOCATION'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('Pageant', 'LOCATION'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('Country', 'O'), ('Superstar', 'O'), ('Trace', 'O'), ('Adkins', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Pop', 'O'), ('Rock', 'O'), ('Sensation', 'O'), ('Boys', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('Girls...', 'O')]
[('Looking', 'O'), ('forward', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('2010', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('Pageant,', 'O'), ('Sunday', 'O'), ('May', 'O'), ('16', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC,', 'O'), ('7', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('ET,', 'O'), ('hosted', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('Curtis', 'PERSON'), ('Stone', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Natalie', 'PERSON'), ('Morales.', 'PERSON')]
[('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('look', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('wife', 'O'), ('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('QVC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('ET', 'O'), ('where', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('debuting', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('jewelry', 'O'), ('collection.', 'O')]
[('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('QVC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('ET', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('introduce', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('beautiful', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('inspiring', 'O'), ('Melania', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Timepieces', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fashion', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Jewelry', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('collection.', 'O')]
[('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('appearing', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Larry', 'O'), ('King', 'O'), ('Live', 'O'), ('tonight,', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('CNN.', 'O'), ('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('conversation!', 'O')]
[('Our', 'O'), ('thoughts', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('prayers', 'O'), ('remain', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Bret', 'PERSON'), ('Michaels', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('family', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('speedy', 'O'), ('recovery.', 'O')]
[('To', 'O'), ('put', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('calendar', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('May:', 'O'), ('Miss', 'O'), ('USA', 'LOCATION'), ('2010,', 'O'), ('live', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Las', 'LOCATION'), ('Vegas', 'LOCATION'), ('on', 'O'), ('May', 'O'), ('16th,', 'O'), ('7', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('ET', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O'), ("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('there--tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('show!', 'O')]
[('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('appearing', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('View', 'O'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('11', 'O'), ('a.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('CBS.', 'O'), ('Tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('fun!', 'O')]
[('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('saw', 'O'), ('American', 'O'), ('Idiot', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Broadway', 'LOCATION'), ('last', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('great.', 'O'), ('An', 'O'), ('amazing', 'O'), ('theatrical', 'O'), ('experience!', 'O')]
[('Tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Marriage', 'O'), ('Ref', 'O'), ('onThursday', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ("NBC--I'm", 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('panel', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('experts', 'O'), ('along', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Gloria', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Estefan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Adam', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Carolla.', 'ORGANIZATION')]
[('On', 'O'), ('Sunday,', 'O'), ('Jerome', 'PERSON'), ('Bettis', 'PERSON'), ("'the", 'O'), ("bus'", 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Pittsburgh', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Steelers', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('will', 'O'), ('play', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ("Int'l", 'LOCATION'), ('Golf', 'LOCATION'), ('ClubPalm', 'LOCATION'), ('Beach', 'LOCATION'), ('against', 'O'), ('Julius', 'PERSON'), ('Erving', 'PERSON'), ("'Dr", 'O'), ("J'", 'O')]
[('"Before', 'O'), ('Kids', 'O'), ('Can', 'O'), ('Go', 'O'), ('Places,', 'O'), ('They', 'O'), ('Need', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Place', 'O'), ('To', 'O'), ('Go"', 'O'), ('--', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('motto', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Police', 'O'), ('Athletic', 'O'), ('League,', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('organization', 'O'), ("I'm", 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('proud', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('support', 'O')]
[('Looking', 'O'), ('forward', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('seeing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('World', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Champion', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Yankees', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('today', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('opening', 'O'), ('day!', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('premiere', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('"Donald', 'O'), ('J.', 'O'), ("Trump's", 'O'), ('Fabulous', 'O'), ('World', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Golf"', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('ET', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Golf', 'O'), ('Channel.', 'O'), ('Tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('adventure!', 'O')]
[('This', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('terrific', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('downtown', 'O'), ('New', 'O'), ('York.', 'O'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('SoHo', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('unlike', 'O'), ('anything', 'O'), ('else.', 'O'), ('Be', 'O'), ('sure', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('visit', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('fantastic', 'O'), ('hotel', 'O'), ('soon!', 'O')]
[('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SoHo', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('opens', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('Friday', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('fantastic!', 'O'), ('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Trump', 'O'), ('Hotel', 'O'), ('Collection...', 'O'), ('http:www.trump.com', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('bestselling', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('April,', 'O'), ('Think', 'O'), ('Like', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Champion,', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('available', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('paperback.', 'O'), ("It's", 'O'), ('inspiring,', 'O'), ('entertaining,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('read.', 'O')]
[('Then', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('attended', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Scottish', 'O'), ('fashion', 'O'), ('show', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('benefits', 'O'), ('veterans,', 'O'), ('Dressed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Kilt', 'O'), ('2010,', 'O'), ('which', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('co-hosted', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Sir', 'O'), ('Sean', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('Lady', 'PERSON'), ('Connery.', 'PERSON')]
[('Last', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('attended', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Skating', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Stars', 'O'), ('Gala', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Wollman', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rink', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('Central', 'O'), ('Park,', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('fantastic.', 'O'), ('Stay', 'O'), ('tuned', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Part', 'O'), ('2..', 'O')]
[("Today's", 'O'), ('open', 'O'), ('call', 'O'), ('drew', 'O'), ('thousands', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('eager', 'O'), ('applicants.', 'O'), ('It', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('impressive', 'O'), ('group,', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('enjoyed', 'O'), ('meeting', 'O'), ('them.', 'O'), ("We've", 'O'), ('got', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('candidates!', 'O')]
[("Don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('open', 'O'), ('call', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice.', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('look', 'O'), ('forward', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('seeing', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('there.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('NYC', 'O'), ('casting', 'O'), ('call', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('thisThursday,', 'O'), ('April', 'O'), ('1', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Tower.', 'O'), ('For', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('information', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('need,', 'O'), ('go', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('NBC.comcasting.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('original', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('coming', 'O'), ('back--do', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('what', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('takes', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('next', 'O'), ('Apprentice?', 'O'), ('For', 'O'), ('casting', 'O'), ('details:', 'O'), ('http:tinyurl.comyly2c8u', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Trump', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hotel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Collection', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('currently', 'O'), ('nominated', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Conde', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nast', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Traveler', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Readers', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Choice', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Awards,', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Travel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Leisure', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('World', 'O'), ('Travel', 'O'), ('Awards.', 'O')]
[('Last', 'O'), ("week's", 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('set', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('stage', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('season.', 'O'), ('Tune', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('Sunday', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('for', 'O'), ('even', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('excitement.', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('am', 'O'), ('happy', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('announce', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('theoriginal', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('--which', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('offer', 'O'), ('job', 'O'), ('opportunities', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('those', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('need--is', 'O'), ('coming', 'O'), ('back.', 'O')]
[('Olympic', 'O'), ('Gold', 'O'), ('Medalist', 'O'), ('Evan', 'PERSON'), ('Lysacek', 'PERSON'), ('just', 'O'), ('left', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('office.', 'O'), ('He', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('town', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('wanted', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('meet', 'O'), ("me--he's", 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('fanastic', 'O'), ('guy', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('true', 'O'), ('champion.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('season', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('start--', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('swept', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('10', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('hour', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('every', 'O'), ('key', 'O'), ('demographic.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('two-hour', 'O'), ('premiere', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('Sunday,', 'O'), ('March', 'O'), ('14th,', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O'), ('This', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('season', 'O'), ('yet,', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('then!', 'O')]
[('From', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump:', 'PERSON'), ('Andrea', 'PERSON'), ('Bocelli', 'PERSON'), ('@', 'O'), ('Mar-a-Lago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('-', 'O'), ('Many', 'O'), ('say', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('entertainment', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('long', 'O'), ('history', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Palm', 'LOCATION'), ('Beach', 'LOCATION'), ('http:bit.ly2fNgOz', 'O')]
[('From', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump:', 'O'), ('“I’m', 'O'), ('so', 'O'), ('proud', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('wife', 'O'), ('Melania', 'PERSON'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('launch', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('jewelry', 'O'), ('line,', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('debut', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('QVC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('on', 'O'), ('April', 'O'), ('30th', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('p.m.”', 'O')]
[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('appeared', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('final', 'O'), ('episode', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Jay', 'PERSON'), ('Leno', 'PERSON'), ('Show', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('deliver', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('special', 'O'), ('message:', 'O'), ('http:bit.lycv1En7', 'O')]
[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('appearing', 'O'), ('today', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('CNN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('International’s', 'O'), ('‘Connect', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('World’', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('‘Connector', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Day’.', 'O'), ('Submit', 'O'), ('questions:', 'O'), ('http:bit.lybPiP7T', 'O')]
[('Superbowl', 'O'), ('Sunday', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('American', 'O'), ('tradition.', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Colts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('Saints', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('already', 'O'), ('champions,', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('may', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('team', 'O'), ('win!', 'O')]
[('Golf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Channel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('&', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Donald', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("Trump's", 'ORGANIZATION'), ('World', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Golf', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('host', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Match', 'O'), ('125', 'O'), ('@', 'O'), ('TNGC', 'O'), ('LA,', 'O'), ('CA', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('Mark', 'PERSON'), ('Wahlberg', 'PERSON'), ('vs.', 'O'), ('Kevin', 'PERSON'), ('Dillon', 'PERSON'), ('http:bit.ly4MubN6', 'O')]
[('from', 'O'), ('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Trump:', 'O'), ('"I', 'O'), ('saw', 'O'), ('Lady', 'PERSON'), ('Gaga', 'PERSON'), ('last', 'O'), ('night', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('fantastic!"', 'O')]
[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Tycoon', 'PERSON'), ('App', 'PERSON'), ('for', 'O'), ('iPhone', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('iPod', 'O'), ('Touch', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ("It's", 'O'), ('$2.99', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('advice', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('priceless!', 'O'), ('http:bit.lyUGUF0', 'O')]
[('Celebrity', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('returns', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('NBC,', 'O'), ('Sunday,', 'O'), ('314,', 'O'), ('9-11PM', 'O'), ('ETPT.', 'O'), ('Outstanding', 'O'), ('list', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('celebrities', 'O'), ('&', 'O'), ('season', 'O'), ('should', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('yet!', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Washington', 'O'), ('Establishment', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('never', 'O'), ('rein', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('government', 'O'), ('spending,', 'O'), ('waste,', 'O'), ('fraud', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('abuse.', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('thinker', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('outsider', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('needed.', 'O')]
[('When', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('government', 'O'), ('finally', 'O'), ('classify', 'O'), ('China', 'LOCATION'), ('as', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('currency', 'O'), ('manipulator?', 'O'), ('China', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('robbing', 'O'), ('us', 'O'), ('blind', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('defends', 'O'), ('them.', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('play', 'O'), ('golf', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('relax.', 'O'), ('My', 'O'), ('company', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('shape.', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('plays', 'O'), ('golf', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('escape', 'O'), ('work', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('America', 'LOCATION'), ('goes', 'O'), ('down', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('drain.', 'O')]
[('NYC', 'O'), ('should', 'O'), ('hold', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('parade', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('returning', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('Afghanistan', 'LOCATION'), ('veterans.', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('like', 'O'), ('Russell', 'PERSON'), ('Brand,', 'PERSON'), ('but', 'O'), ('Katy', 'PERSON'), ('Perry', 'PERSON'), ('made', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('big', 'O'), ('mistake', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('married', 'O'), ('him.', 'O'), ("Let's", 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('if', 'O'), ("I'm", 'O'), ('right---I', 'O'), ('hope', 'O'), ('not.', 'O')]
[('America', 'LOCATION'), ('wasted', 'O'), ('billions', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('precious', 'O'), ('lives', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('will', 'O'), ('soon', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('control--very', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('sad.', 'O')]
[("I'm", 'O'), ('right,', 'O'), ('TPM', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('wrong', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('did', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('issue', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('special', 'O'), ('statement', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Christmas--however', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('issued', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coFflwOekU', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Mar-a-Lago', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Club', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('has', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('meatloaf', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('America.', 'O'), ('Tasty.', 'O'), ('http:t.co3GS8TRgM', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('predicted', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('911', 'O'), ('attack', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('America', 'LOCATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('"The', 'O'), ('America', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('Deserve"', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('collapse', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('@TimeToGetTough.', 'O')]
[('Americans', 'O'), ('Elect', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('track', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('put', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('Indy', 'O'), ('Presidential', 'O'), ('candidate', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ballot', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('50', 'O'), ('states.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('destroying', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('country:@BarackObama', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('requested', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('raise', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('debt', 'O'), ('limit', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('$16.4Trillion', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coA5DGJvhP', 'O')]
[('"It\'s', 'O'), ('important', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('help', 'O'), ('poor', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('become', 'O'), ('independent,', 'O'), ('self-sufficient', 'O'), ('individuals', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('gain', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('benefits', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('work."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('China', 'LOCATION'), ('has', 'O'), ('5', 'O'), ('oil', 'O'), ('projects', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ("didn't", 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('anything', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Iraqis', 'O'), ('except', 'O'), ('asked', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('leave.', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('going', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coKhujI5YC', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ("Fed's", 'O'), ('reckless', 'O'), ('monetary', 'O'), ('policies', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('cause', 'O'), ('problems', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('years', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('come.', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('Fed', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('has', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('reined', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('or', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('soon', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('Greece.', 'O')]
[('What', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('convenient', 'O'), ('mistake:', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('issued', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('statement', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Kwanza', 'LOCATION'), ('but', 'O'), ('failed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('issue', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Christmas.', 'O'), ('http:t.coDodG53Rx', 'O')]
[('Vote', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('favorite', 'O'), ('TRUMP', 'O'), ('HOTEL', 'O'), ('COLLECTION', 'O'), ('hotels', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Travel', 'O'), ('+', 'O'), ('Leisure’s', 'O'), ('2012', 'O'), ('World’s', 'O'), ('Best', 'O'), ('Awards', 'O'), ('Survey', 'O'), ('http:t.co173fGaoU', 'O')]
[('@TrumpCollection', 'O'), ('tops', 'O'), ('@TravlandLeisure', 'O'), ('500', 'O'), ('Best', 'O'), ('Hotels', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('World!', 'O'), ('Congrats', 'O'), ('@TrumpNewYork,', 'O'), ('@TrumpLasVegas,', 'O'), ('@TrumpChicago,', 'O'), ('@TrumpSoHo', 'O')]
[('China', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('expanding', 'O'), ('its', 'O'), ('military', 'O'), ('bases', 'O'), ('abroad.', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('must', 'O'), ('expand', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('naval', 'O'), ('fleet.', 'O'), ('Now', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('no', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('defense', 'O'), ('cuts.', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coSSvY2HNh', 'O')]
[('China', 'LOCATION'), ('hacked', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('U.S.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chamber', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('of', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Commerce', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('and', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('information', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('3', 'O'), ('million', 'O'), ('members.', 'O'), ('China', 'LOCATION'), ('keeps', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.cov4rOQ4jk', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Keystone', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('pipeline', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('create', 'O'), ('20,000', 'O'), ('jobs', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('lower', 'O'), ('gas', 'O'), ('prices.', 'O'), ('But', 'O'), ('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('says', 'O'), ('No.', 'O'), ('Dumb.', 'O')]
[('Govt.', 'O'), ('collapsing', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('only', 'O'), ('2', 'O'), ('weeks', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('withdrawal', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('troops.', 'O'), ('Sadly,', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('called', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('please', 'O'), ('remember,', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('alone', 'O'), ('called', 'O'), ('it.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('habitual', 'O'), ('vacationer,', 'O'), ('@BarackObama,', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Hawaii.', 'O'), ('This', 'O'), ('vacation', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('costing', 'O'), ('taxpayers', 'O'), ('$4', 'O'), ('milion', 'O'), ('+++', 'O'), ('while', 'O'), ('there', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('20%', 'O'), ('unemployment.', 'O')]
[('In', 'O'), ('order', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('preserve', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('options', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('guarantee', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('defeated,', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('changed', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('voter', 'O'), ('registration', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('independent.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Keystone', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('pipeline', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('create', 'O'), ('20,000', 'O'), ('jobs', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('us', 'O'), ('less', 'O'), ('energy', 'O'), ('dependent', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Middle', 'O'), ('East.', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('No!', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('safest', 'O'), ('way', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('preserve', 'O'), ('Medicare', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('robust', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('vibrant', 'O'), ('economy.', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('should', 'O'), ('lower', 'O'), ('corporate', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('capital', 'O'), ('gain', 'O'), ('taxes', 'O'), ('immediately.', 'O')]
[('A', 'O'), ('week', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('says', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('enemy,', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('demand', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('pay', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('9', 'O'), ('year', 'O'), ('occupation.', 'O'), ('http:t.coy2dRr57G', 'O')]
[('Even', 'O'), ('if', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('stays', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('DC,', 'O'), ('taxpayers', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('pay', 'O'), ('millions', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('Hawaii', 'LOCATION'), ('vacation', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('Americans', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('struggling', 'O'), ('http:t.coeKd7gzXI', 'O')]
[('“Consider', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('fact', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('every', 'O'), ('gallon', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('gas', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('put', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('car,', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('pay', 'O'), ('45.8', 'O'), ('cents', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('state,', 'O'), ('local,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('federal', 'O'), ('taxes.”', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('“The', 'O'), ('thing', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('high', 'O'), ('corporate', 'O'), ('tax', 'O'), ('rates', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('that,', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('end,', 'O'), ('companies', 'O'), ('aren’t', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ones', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('foot', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('bill,', 'O'), ('consumers', 'O'), ('do.”', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('“We', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('president', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('vendetta', 'O'), ('against', 'O'), ('businesspeople', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('considers', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('enemy.', 'O'), ('He’s', 'O'), ('also', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coCELNUe0O', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('present', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('holiday', 'O'), ('season.', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('gift', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('anyone', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('cares', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('country.', 'O')]
[('Less', 'O'), ('than', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('week', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('leave', 'O'), ('Iraq,', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('country', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('already', 'O'), ('unraveling.', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('got', 'O'), ('nothing', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Iraqis', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coxeI2wDHk', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('@FoxNews', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('@gretawire', 'O'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('delusional', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('3rd', 'O'), ('party', 'O'), ('candidate', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('win.', 'O'), ('http:t.colLvVLX4E', 'O')]
[('Barney', 'PERSON'), ('Frank', 'PERSON'), ('looked', 'O'), ('disgusting--nipples', 'O'), ('protruding--in', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('blue', 'O'), ('shirt', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('Congress.', 'O'), ('Very', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('disrespectful.', 'O')]
[('Congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('@AmericansElect', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('winning', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('spot', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('California', 'LOCATION'), ('2012', 'O'), ('ballot.', 'O'), ('A', 'O'), ('major', 'O'), ('feat!', 'O'), ('http:t.coXjugMNK9', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('delusional:', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('believes', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('4th', 'O'), ('best', 'O'), ('POTUS', 'O'), ('ever.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('WH', 'O'), ('yesterday', 'O'), ('defended', 'O'), ("Biden's", 'O'), ('comments', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("aren't", 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('enemy.', 'O'), ('When', 'O'), ('did', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('American', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('decide', 'O'), ('this?', 'O'), ('http:t.covP4bo45p', 'O')]
[('"Obamacare', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('killed', 'O'), ('now', 'O'), ('before', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('grows', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('an', 'O'), ('even', 'O'), ('bigger', 'O'), ('mess,', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('inevitably', 'O'), ('will."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('"The', 'O'), ('sad', 'O'), ('truth', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('some', 'O'), ('Republicans', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Congress', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('are', 'O'), ('clueless', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('comes', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('negotiation."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('really', 'O'), ('enjoyed', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ("night's", 'O'), ('Tele-Town', 'O'), ('Hall', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ("@ralphreed's", 'O'), ('Faith', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Freedom', 'O'), ('Coalition.', 'O'), ('Thanks', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('thousands', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('joined.', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('still', 'O'), ("can't", 'O'), ('believe', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ("didn't", 'O'), ('t', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('oil', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('Iraq.', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('@ASavageNation', 'O'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough,', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('2012', 'O'), ('plans', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('http:t.coIgnuA6M8', 'O'), ('http:t.coBq0GXn1j', 'O')]
[('For', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('minute', 'O'), ('shopping,', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('choice...http:amzn.tosNqlFH', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('average', 'O'), ('family', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('spent', 'O'), ('$4,155', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('year', 'O'), ('filling', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('car', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('$3.50gallon', 'O'), ('average.', 'O'), ('Both', 'O'), ('record', 'O'), ('highs.', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coTdkHJRKA', 'O')]
[('Tom', 'PERSON'), ('"marbles', 'PERSON'), ('in', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('mouth"', 'O'), ('Brokaw', 'PERSON'), ('once', 'O'), ('thanked', 'O'), ('me', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('success', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Apprentice', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('NBC.', 'O'), ('Now,', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('calls', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coKB1FinI0', 'O')]
[('Joe', 'PERSON'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('said', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Taliban', 'ORGANIZATION'), ("'is", 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ("enemy.'", 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('wonder', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('troops', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Afghanistant', 'LOCATION'), ('that', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('under', 'O'), ('attack', 'O'), ('view', 'O'), ("Biden's", 'O'), ('statement.', 'O')]
[('What', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('shock!', 'O'), ('The', 'O'), ('U.S.', 'LOCATION'), ('Capitol', 'O'), ('Christmas', 'O'), ('tree', 'O'), ('pays', 'O'), ('homage', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('failed', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('mention', 'O'), ('Jesus.', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('thinks', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('wealth', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('create', 'O'), ('belongs', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ("gov't.", 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ("doesn't", 'O'), ('respect', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('fact', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('money', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('wastes', 'O'), ('belongs', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('us.', 'O')]
[('"He', 'O'), ('thinks', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('wealth', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('create', 'O'), ('belongs', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('government--@BarackObama', 'O'), ("doesn't", 'O'), ('respect', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('fact', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coD66nscyB', 'O')]
[('"People', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ability', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('work', 'O'), ('should.', 'O'), ('But', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('government', 'O'), ('happy', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('send', 'O'), ('checks,', 'O'), ('too', 'O'), ('many', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('don\'t."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('"When', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('going', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('wake', 'O'), ('up', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('realize', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('funding', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('enemies?"', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('A', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('gift', 'O'), ('idea', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough,', 'O'), ('easy', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('order', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('Amazon', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('http:t.coV6RmNj7x', 'O')]
[("We're", 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('proud', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('@erictrump', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('@Forbes', 'O'), ('30', 'O'), ('Under', 'O'), ('30', 'O'), ('list.', 'O'), ('http:t.coKZQuLCMj', 'O')]
[('"It\'s', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('plain', 'O'), ('fact:', 'O'), ('free', 'O'), ('trade', 'O'), ('requires', 'O'), ('having', 'O'), ('fair', 'O'), ('rules', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('apply', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('everyone."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('"We', 'O'), ('need', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('tax', 'O'), ('system', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('fair', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('smart--one', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('encourages', 'O'), ('growth,', 'O'), ('savings,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('investment."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('China', 'LOCATION'), ('taxing', 'O'), ('imports', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('--22%--', 'O'), ('why', 'O'), ("aren't", 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('taxing', 'O'), ('China?', 'O')]
[('Dummies', 'O'), ('left', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('without', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('oil--not', 'O'), ('believable!', 'O')]
[('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('political', 'O'), ('turmoil', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), ('after', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('leave---I', 'O'), ('told', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('so.', 'O')]
[('Congratulations', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('son', 'O'), ('Eric', 'PERSON'), ('for', 'O'), ('making', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Forbes', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('30', 'O'), ('under', 'O'), ('30', 'O'), ('list.', 'O'), ("He's", 'O'), ('done', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('job!', 'O'), ('http:t.coYDEIKzG6', 'O')]
[('Barney', 'PERSON'), ('Frank', 'PERSON'), ('admited', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('ObamaCare', 'O'), ('does', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ("'death", 'O'), ("panels'", 'O'), ('yesterday.', 'O'), ('Obamacare', 'O'), ('must', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('fully', 'O'), ('repealed', 'O'), ('or', 'O'), ('healthcare', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('destroyed.', 'O')]
[('With', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('record', 'O'), ('deficit', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('$15', 'O'), ('trillion', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('debt,', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('spending', 'O'), ('$4', 'O'), ('million', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('money', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('Hawaii', 'LOCATION'), ('vacation.', 'O'), ('Just', 'O'), ('plain', 'O'), ('wrong.', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('Dean', 'PERSON'), ('on', 'O'), ('@americanowradio-', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('told', 'O'), ('him', 'O'), ('what', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('really', 'O'), ('thought', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('@FoxNews', 'O'), ('debate.', 'O'), ('http:t.co2B7fY0WI', 'O')]
[("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('@americanowradio', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('Dean', 'PERSON'), ('at', 'O'), ('6:30', 'O'), ('ET', 'O'), ('today', 'O'), ('talking', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ("night's", 'O'), ('@FoxNews', 'O'), ('debate.', 'O'), ('http:t.coowXU5vwh', 'O')]
[('OPEC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('setting', 'O'), ('crude', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('$94barrel', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ("'signs", 'O'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('economy', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ("improving.'", 'O'), ('OPEC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('uses', 'O'), ('any', 'O'), ('excuse', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('rip', 'O'), ('us', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('leaders', 'O'), ('just', 'O'), ('watch.', 'O')]
[('China', 'LOCATION'), ('just', 'O'), ('put', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('tariff', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('US', 'LOCATION'), ('cars', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('trucks--22%--China', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('laughing', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('inept', 'O'), ('leaders.', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('lightweight,', 'O'), ('@JonHuntsman,', 'O'), ('used', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('name', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('debate', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('gravitas--it', 'O'), ("didn't", 'O'), ('work.', 'O'), ('Sad!', 'O')]
[('A', 'O'), ('total', 'O'), ('lightweight:', 'O'), ('@JonHuntsman', 'O'), ('continues', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('give', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('worst', 'O'), ('responses', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('China', 'LOCATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('debates.', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('why', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coYwKcaMf0', 'O')]
[('Great', 'O'), ('@Esquiremag', 'O'), ('piece', 'O'), ('-', 'O'), ("'@DonaldJTrumpJr:", 'O'), ('What', 'O'), ("I've", 'O'), ("Learned'", 'O'), ('http:t.col8SK99ww', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('@BarbaraJWalters', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('her', 'O'), ('@ABC', 'O'), ('special', 'O'), ("'Most", 'O'), ('Fascinating', 'O'), ('People', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ("2011'", 'O'), ('http:t.co9oo3YzMB', 'O')]
[('But', 'O'), ('maybe', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('biggest', 'O'), ('beef', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Obama', 'PERSON'), ('is', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('view', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ("there's", 'O'), ('nothing', 'O'), ('special', 'O'), ('or', 'O'), ('exceptional', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('America.', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('Your', 'O'), ('civil', 'O'), ('liberties', 'O'), ('mean', 'O'), ('nothing', 'O'), ('if', 'O'), ("you're", 'O'), ('dead.', 'O'), ("That's", 'O'), ('why', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('single', 'O'), ('most', 'O'), ('important', 'O'), ('function', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('federal', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coNc2SuTOf', 'O')]
[('"I', 'O'), ('believe', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('rock', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('lot', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('people.', 'O'), ("Don't", 'O'), ('just', 'O'), ('read', 'O'), ('#TImeToGetTough', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('share', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('friends', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('family!"', 'O'), ('-RushLimbaugh', 'O')]
[('Thanks', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('everyone', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('waited', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('long', 'O'), ('lines', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('signings.', 'O'), ('It', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('meet', 'O'), ('fellow', 'O'), ('patriots.', 'O')]
[('So', 'O'), ('biased:', 'O'), ('@TIME', 'O'), ('made', 'O'), ("'The", 'O'), ("Protester'", 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('person', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('year.', 'O'), ('@TIME', 'O'), ('celebrates', 'O'), ('OWS', 'O'), ('but', 'O'), ('vilified', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Tea', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Party', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('last', 'O'), ('year.', 'O')]
[('This', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('what', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('thinks:', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('America', 'LOCATION'), ('would', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('better', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('if', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('acted', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('like', 'O'), ('European', 'O'), ('socialist', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coYbFa0LD6', 'O')]
[('If', 'O'), ('speeches', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('memoirs', 'O'), ('created', 'O'), ('jobs', 'O'), ('then', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('would', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('Ronald', 'PERSON'), ('Reagan.', 'PERSON')]
[('#trumpvlog', 'O'), ('China', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('laughing....', 'O'), ('http:t.co9ghflFLP', 'O')]
[('Please', 'O'), ('send', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('psychiatrist', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('help', 'O'), ('@Rosie,', 'O'), ('she’s', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('bad', 'O'), ('state.', 'O'), ('To', 'O'), ('@Rosie’s', 'O'), ('girlfriend’s', 'O'), ('parents---', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.co1c9yApM4', 'O')]
[('More', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('attend', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('@JonHuntsman', 'O'), ('rally', 'O'), ('than', 'O'), ('watch', 'O'), ('@Lawrence', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('@MSNBCtv', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('week.', 'O'), ('@Lawrence', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('lonely.', 'O'), ('(cont)', 'O'), ('http:t.coF3PJhZnr', 'O')]
[('With', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('number', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('tweets', 'O'), ('sad', 'O'), ('sack', 'O'), ('@Rosie', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('done,', 'O'), ('she', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('totally', 'O'), ('lost', 'O'), ('control', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('herself--', 'O'), ('hopefully', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('breakdown.', 'O')]
[('#noratings', 'O'), ('@Lawrence', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('soon', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('tv-', 'O'), ('bad', 'O'), ('ratings-', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('face', 'O'), ('made', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('radio.', 'O')]
[('"Let', 'O'), ('me', 'O'), ('put', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('plainly', 'O'), ('as', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('know', 'O'), ('how:', 'O'), ("Iran's", 'O'), ('nuclear', 'O'), ('program', 'O'), ('must', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('stopped--by', 'O'), ('any', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('means', 'O'), ('necessary.', 'O'), ('Period."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('It', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('meet', 'O'), ('fellow', 'O'), ('patriots', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('signings.', 'O'), ("Can't", 'O'), ('wait', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('meet', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('today', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION'), ('from', 'O'), ('12PM', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('2PM', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('signing', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION'), ('for', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('was', 'O'), ('so', 'O'), ('popular', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ("I'm", 'O'), ('doing', 'O'), ('another', 'O'), ('one', 'O'), ('today', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('noon', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('2pmTrump', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION')]
[('Hope', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION'), ('(5th', 'O'), ('Ave', 'O'), ('betw', 'O'), ('56', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('57)', 'O'), ('--', 'O'), ("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('signing', 'O'), ('copies', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('noon', 'O'), ('until', 'O'), ('2', 'O'), ('pm', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('habitual', 'O'), ('vacationer,', 'O'), ('@BarackObama,', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('sacrificed', 'O'), ('so', 'O'), ('much.', 'O'), ('He', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('delaying', 'O'), ('his', 'O'), ('17', 'O'), ('day', 'O'), ('Hawaii', 'LOCATION'), ('vacation', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('couple', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('hours.', 'O')]
[('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('closing', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Strait', 'LOCATION'), ('of', 'LOCATION'), ('Hormuz', 'LOCATION'), ('for', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('military', 'O'), ('exercise.', 'O'), ('Imagine', 'O'), ('what', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('do', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('nukes?!', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Mullahs', 'O'), ('laughed', 'O'), ('when', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('"asked"', 'O'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('to', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('drone--they', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('show', 'O'), ('it', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('China', 'LOCATION'), ('first.', 'O')]
[('"We', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('combat', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('welfare', 'O'), ('mentality', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('individuals', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('entitled', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('live', 'O'), ('off', 'O'), ('taxpayers."', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('It', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('great', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('meet', 'O'), ('so', 'O'), ('many', 'O'), ('wonderful', 'O'), ('people', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('signings.', 'O'), ('Anyone', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('wants', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('Prez', 'O'), ('should', 'O'), ('read!', 'O')]
[('"So,', 'O'), ('if', 'O'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('is', 'O'), ('going', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('oil,', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('say', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('take', 'O'), ('over', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('oil', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('by', 'O'), ('hammering', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('cost-sharing', 'O'), ('plan', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('Iraq."#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('Read', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('about', 'O'), ('@lawrence......', 'O'), ('http:t.cor7JWwoAY', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('@EWErickson', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('@RedState', 'O'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough,', 'O'), ('GOP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('primary', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('2012', 'O'), ('options', 'O'), ('http:t.coSD6NqxZR', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('@FoxNews', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('@gretawire', 'O'), ('explaining', 'O'), ('that', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('am', 'O'), ('keeping', 'O'), ('all', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('options', 'O'), ('available', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('2012', 'O'), ('http:t.coKq7FKBnc', 'O')]
[('Save', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('time', 'O'), ('@rosie', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('focus', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('your', 'O'), ('horrible', 'O'), ('ratings,', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ("don't", 'O'), ('mention', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('name', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('talk', 'O'), ('shows', 'O'), ('anymore', 'O'), ('or', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('more', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('same.', 'O')]
[('#badratings', 'O'), ('@Rosie', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('never', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('it.', 'O'), ('You', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('funny', 'O'), ('or', 'O'), ('talented.', 'O')]
[('#badratings', 'O'), ("@Lawrence's", 'O'), ('show', 'O'), ('failed', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('8pm', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('failing(even', 'O'), ('worse)', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('10pm-', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('long', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('tv.....', 'O')]
[('I', 'O'), ('feel', 'O'), ('sorry', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Rosie', 'PERSON'), ("'s", 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('partner', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('love', 'O'), ('whose', 'O'), ('parents', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('devastated', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('thought', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('their', 'O'), ('daughter', 'O'), ('being', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('@Rosie--a', 'O'), ('true', 'O'), ('loser.', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('@FoxNews', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('@TeamCavuto', 'O'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('why', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('not', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('moderating', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Newsmax-@iontv', 'O'), ('debate', 'O'), ('http:t.coGWGw43UH', 'O')]
[('Check', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('"Time', 'O'), ('To', 'O'), ('Get', 'O'), ('Tough:', 'O'), ('Making', 'O'), ('America', 'O'), ('#1', 'O'), ('Again"', 'O'), ('http:t.coVEEHngHq', 'O')]
[('Thousands', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('e-mails', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('folks', 'O'), ('urging', 'O'), ('me', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('seek', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Americans', 'O'), ('Elect', 'O'), ('Presidential', 'O'), ('nomination.', 'O')]
[('#trumpvlog', 'O'), ('Same', 'O'), ('last', 'O'), ('name,', 'O'), ('same', 'O'), ('bad', 'O'), ('ratings-', 'O'), ('@lawrence', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('@rosie.....', 'O'), ('http:t.coKCVRNBJa', 'O')]
[('He', 'O'), ('says', 'O'), ('he', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('spend', 'O'), ('$1', 'O'), ('B', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('get', 'O'), ('re-elected:', 'O'), ('@BarackObama.', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('can', 'O'), ('match', 'O'), ('him--preserving', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('options.', 'O')]
[("I'll", 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('signing', 'O'), ('copies', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('new', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('@TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('tomorrow', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Trump', 'LOCATION'), ('Tower', 'LOCATION'), ('(5th', 'LOCATION'), ('Avenue', 'LOCATION'), ('between', 'O'), ('56', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('57)', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('noon', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('2pm.', 'O')]
[('Real', 'O'), ('unemployment', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('20%.', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('must', 'O'), ('simplify', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('tax', 'O'), ('code', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('start', 'O'), ('making', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('own', 'O'), ('products', 'O'), ('again', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('bring', 'O'), ('our', 'O'), ('jobs', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('overseas.', 'O')]
[('#trumpvlog', 'O'), ('NY', 'O'), ('Area-', 'O'), ('Two', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('signings-', 'O'), ('Tonight', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('Thursday....', 'O'), ('http:t.covaJaeKjf', 'O')]
[('Who', 'O'), ('handed', 'O'), ('Iraq', 'LOCATION'), ('over', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('yesterday?', 'O'), ('@BarackObama.', 'O'), ('We', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('gotten', 'O'), ('nothing', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Iraqis--', 'O'), ('we', 'O'), ('should', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('them', 'O'), ('pay', 'O'), ('us', 'O'), ('back', 'O'), ('with', 'O'), ('oil.', 'O')]
[('#trumpvlog', 'O'), ('Why', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('cancelled', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('"great', 'O'), ('debate".....', 'O'), ('http:t.coPO61leR7', 'O')]
[("Don't", 'O'), ('forget', 'O'), ('my', 'O'), ('book', 'O'), ('signing', 'O'), ('tonight', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('Costco', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('on', 'O'), ('1250', 'O'), ('Old', 'LOCATION'), ('Country', 'LOCATION'), ('Road', 'LOCATION'), ('in', 'O'), ('Westbury,', 'O'), ('NY,', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('6-8', 'O'), ('pm.', 'O'), ('Hope', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('see', 'O'), ('you', 'O'), ('there.', 'O')]
[('The', 'O'), ('Mullahs', 'O'), ('are', 'O'), ('laughing', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('what', 'O'), ('they', 'O'), ('think', 'O'), ('is', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('very', 'O'), ('stupid', 'O'), ('president,@BarackObama', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('"asked"', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('Iran', 'LOCATION'), ('to', 'O'), ('return', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('drone', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('Look,', 'O'), ("here's", 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('deal:', 'O'), ('@BarackObama', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('total', 'O'), ('disaster.', 'O'), ('He', 'O'), ('has', 'O'), ('spent', 'O'), ('this', 'O'), ('country', 'O'), ('into', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('ground', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('destroyed', 'O'), ('jobs', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O')]
[('We', 'O'), ('need', 'O'), ('a', 'O'), ('dealmaker', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('White', 'O'), ('House,', 'O'), ('who', 'O'), ('knows', 'O'), ('how', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('think', 'O'), ('innovatively', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('make', 'O'), ('smart', 'O'), ('deals.', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough.', 'O')]
[('Tonight', 'O'), ('I', 'O'), ('will', 'O'), ('be', 'O'), ('signing', 'O'), ('copies', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('Westbury', 'LOCATION'), ('at', 'O'), ('Costco,', 'O'), ('1250', 'O'), ('Old', 'O'), ('Country', 'O'), ('Rd,', 'O'), ('from', 'O'), ('6', 'O'), ('pm', 'O'), ('to', 'O'), ('8', 'O'), ('pm', 'O')]
[('@Amazon', 'O'), ('sold', 'O'), ('out', 'O'), ('of', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough', 'O'), ('in', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('first', 'O'), ('week.', 'O'), ('More', 'O'), ('copies', 'O'), ('have', 'O'), ('been', 'O'), ('ordered', 'O'), ('for', 'O'), ('holidays.', 'O'), ("Don't", 'O'), ('worry.', 'O')]
[('My', 'O'), ('interview', 'O'), ('on', 'O'), ('@theviewtv', 'O'), ('discussing', 'O'), ('#TimeToGetTough,', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('GOP', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('primary', 'O'), ('and', 'O'), ('the', 'O'), ('Newsmax-@iontv', 'O'), ('debate(starts', 'O'), ('at', 'O'), ('23:00)', 'O'), ('http:t.coROcUyAXe', 'O')]
